brandpa.com 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy

Privacy matters but it can be confusing. This page explains our approach to privacy on Brandpa's website and how it affects you. 

## Summary

  * We collect anonymous statistics about your visit, like counting which pages you viewed. 
  * We use [Facebook's advertising network](https://www.facebook.com/Business-Ads). Facebook measures when you use certain features of our website, to determine if an advert is working. 
  * We never share any personally identifiable information with 3rd parties except to help us deliver our own services. 

These are just the key points. If you need detail, keep reading. 

##  Visitors to this website 

This website records anonymous statistics about what pages are viewed, what searches are made, and what features are used. We use this information to measure the popularity of individual domain names, and to prevent abuse (e.g. detect bots, spam, fake purchases etc). This information is stored anonymously, which means we don't record your name, IP address, or anything else which could identify you personally. 

We also measure visitors to our website using [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/). Google records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. Again, all of that information is anonymous – so we don’t know _who_ you are; just that _somebody_ visited our site. 

We use [Facebook's advertising network](https://www.facebook.com/Business-Ads), which means Facebook can measure your use of specific features on the Brandpa website. They use this to determine whether an advert results in conversions. They also use this to determine whether a visitor to Brandpa could be shown relevant adverts later, e.g. for a domain name that they looked at. Brandpa does not have access to any personally identifiable information gathered during this process. 

We use [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) for processing credit cards. Stripe use cookies to help identify suspicious behaviour before a purchase is made, such as non-human purchases. This information is not visible to Brandpa. 

We use Google's [reCAPTCHA](https://www.google.com/recaptcha) to detect bots and spam, e.g. fake offers or purchases. reCAPTCHA uses cookies to track your behaviour on this site and determine if you are probably human. This information is not visible to Brandpa. 

Our website is hosted by [Amazon Web Services](https://aws.amazon.com/). All data we store on AWS is protected via two-factor authentication and only available to authorised developers. 

##  Making an offer, enquiry or purchase 

If you make an offer, enquiry or purchase a domain name, we will ask you for some personally identifiable information, which is required to perform that service. For example, your address is required to complete a purchase. 

We use [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) for handling all credit card transactions. Brandpa never have any access to your payment information, but we do have access to your name, address and email, which we require to fulfil your order. 

We use [ZenDesk](https://zendesk.com/) and [GSuite](https://gsuite.google.com/) internally to provide support and communicate to you. 

We delete all personally identifiable information (e.g. name, address, IP address) from all offers, enquiries or purchases within 12 months of them last being used. 

##  Becoming a seller or designer 

To become a seller or designer on Brandpa, you are asked to provide your email address, and to receive payments you may also provide a PayPal email address or bank transfer details. These are required for Brandpa to pay you. 

As a seller or designer we may send you relevant and necessary service emails, such as notifying you that your domains have been listed, sold, or suspended. We will also notify you of new or altered features that impact you as a seller or designer on Brandpa. We do _not_ send you marketing emails. 

We never provide your personal information or email address to any third parties except where they are specifically employed to help deliver our own services. 

If you choose to close your account Brandpa will remove all of your personally identifiable information. We will still retain a record of the domains that you may have sold or designed, but in an anonymous manner. 

## Security

Brandpa take many precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. All personal information you provide us with is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Access to all data is tightly controlled and where possible protected via two-factor authentication. 

## Cookies

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is simply a technology for remembering something about you. We use cookies to improve your browsing experience as well as understand your preferences for future visits.

You can turn cookies off but you'll need to know that by doing so some features on our site may be disabled. You can read more about cookies on [Cookies and You](http://cookies.insites.com/).

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or your personal data, please write to us: [info@brandpa.com](mailto:info@brandpa.com).
